<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<books>
<book ID="BookbyBread" Title="{{W|Tyrannosaurus Revs: Official Strategy Guide}}" Format="Auto" Margins="1,2,2,2">
  <page>{{C|Foreword: The Library of the Narrow-Eyed Council of Ulep, Manuscript 44 Archive D, also called Perma XI and commonly known as Dinosaur Revs is one of the few existing references to computerized multimedia from ancient days. It presents techniques and instruction in reference to a work of lost media, apparently surrounding a motif of combat between archosaurs using contemporary motorized carriages. Mentioned in no other historical sources, it was most likely devised during the earliest advent of microcomputers. The following presentation was composed by Da Fly on behalf of Grackle of Three Strings. It was determined that Grackle's presentation was the best and most thorough translation available. Most of the work is translated in such a way so as to leave the original arrangement intact, aside from structural changes to improve suitability for this format. The majority of the pages were either never recovered, or illegible, and will not be included in this edition.}}


{{y|Preface by Grackle: The cultural and industrial preeminence of The Eaters is a fact well-established among the learned folk in Qud. Yet even thousands of years ago, the Earth beneath the average Eater's feet contained more closed chapters than the average soul will ever so much as open. Irritatingly, entropy has rendered the majority of these chapters permanently closed. Sources like Tyrannosaurus Revs are perhaps the most irritating of all. It is a cave painting if you will, or an index collected from a burnt library; a source of commentary telling us only of something we will never be able to study, touch, reconstruct, or experience in any other way. As a historian, I've spent too many hours of my life harrassed by daydreams of playing this game, knowing that I never will. I can only pray that after I am long dead and decomposed, our descendents will feel some wonder at the culture I was part of.}}



Introduction, the basics:
Be glad you have the Tyrannosaurus Revs: Official Strategy Guide stashed in your glove box, because this game's competition is outright cretaceous! Between these covers are all the pro-gaming secrets that make the difference between evolution and extinction. You'll learn how to read ECU data from a rolling dino, turn flintstone jalopies into death-chariots, and how to drift like a continent.

[The guide pivots into a walkthrough of the first-time initialization of the game, and a tour of the basic procedures of a typical session accompanied by printed screenshots. Many pages are missing from this section. The author notes that much speculation may be made on the content of the missing pages]

The Arsenal: This game contains firepower that makes the chicxulub impactor look like a nerf dart, and we're not afraid to use it. These vehicle parts are highly sought-after during the looting stage, and are extremely rewarding to install. Yet elite players are often seen reaching the final round with nothing but firelances, why? The answer is obvious: while the dweebenheimers are scrambling over who has the biggest gun, not only are they constantly competing, but they neglect the platform it's mounted on. Was it not Sun-Tzu who said that in war, one is to avoid what is strong and strike what is weak? Not only are you yourself fighting for what is most contested, thus costing yourself many other opportunities. Furthermore, you will lack the most important thing about a war-wagon: the speed to escape and intercept! Therefore, you must balance mobility and the ability to use the environment versus the ability to win in a strict one-on-one contest.

[The guide ends, punctuated with a glossary, including a glossary of contemporary jargon translated by the author, an index, listing many of the unrecovered pages, and a picture of what appears to be a contemporary electronic device, which the author claims is an advertisement.]
  </page>
</book>
</books>