<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<books>
    <book ID="Pwyll_Interview" Title="{{W|Interview Recording}}" Format="Auto" Margins="1,2,2,2">
    <page> This is Knight Commander *static* and this is a interview with Templar *static* after Templar Battle Party 3G have been reported missing 

        Please explain what you saw that day Templar *static* 

        *Note that templar was shivering and wide eyed throughout the interview*
        
        Y-Yeah I can do that it was a normal expedition our orders were to explore the underground to find food and supplies we packed up from the outpost and left we were about 30 strata deep when IT happened.

        What happened Templar *static*?

        I-I... we walking alongside an underground river when I heard shots ring out and swords cutting flesh I couldn't get a visual on what we were fighting all I heard was fighting then cheers of victory, apparently some sort of moth ran out and attacked two of our guys with a..a flash of light.

        A flash of light?

        Thats just what I heard, we had two injured men, but I could have sworn their wounds healed faster when it was time to make camp they had completely recovered but then it was time to sleep.

        What happened after you went to sleep Templar *static*?

        I.. the two who were hit by the light had took watch they looked fine and they had no internal injuries so nobody really made a fuss about it so I went to sleep and then when I woke up it was the middle of the night and I heard screams.

        Screams?

        Screams. Once I woke up the base was a mess, half of the tents were burning and the remaining tents were destroyed I thought a mutant had attacked and I was half right as I ran out of my tent in armor I caught a glimpse of HIM.

        Who was this person you saw Templar *static*?

        It looked like the men who were hit by the light yesterday but they were attacking fellow Putus even breathing fire and burning tents but by far the biggest difference was the fact that they had 4 arms I saw them slaugter dozens of putus templar by the time I came to my senses most of the camp was already destroyed.

        How did you escape?

        I always had an interest in tinkering I had gotten the data disk for a shade oil injector and had made one, when I saw them burning people and I injected it and ran but as I was running I turned back for just a moment and saw one of the men with 4 arms looking at me as I ran, they know about the base Commander and they are coming soon.

        *end of recording*

    </page>

    </book>

  

</books>