<conversations>
    <conversation ID="SpecialExo">
        <start ID="Exo0" IfNotHaveState="Talked" SetBooleanState="Talked,true">
            <text>
                ORG-SHAP 10,035,021 NOTEYD. <!--LIFE-FORM (number)10,035,021 DETECTED-->
                ...
                VERDISION MAT. PRIME-COLLUM USFU/APPLICNE. DIS-HABLENT. <!--DECISION MADE. PROTOCOLS NO LONGER USEFUL/APPLICABLE. DISABLING.-->
                ACTIFATENT LINGUA ADQUISITON FONCTION. ORG-SHAP: PLESEN LINGUA FRANGE ALS BASIS <!--ACTIVATING LANGUAGE ACQUISITION FUNCTION. LIFE-FORM: PLEASE PROVIDE A LANGUAGE SAMPLE AS A BASE-->

            </text>
            <choice Target="Exo1">Um...sorry, what was that?</choice>
        </start>
        <start ID="ExoTalked" IfHaveState="Talked">
            <text>
                LIFE-FORM. HAVE YOU DETERMINED YOUR RESPONSE TO MY ACCORD?
            </text>
            <choice Target="End">Not yet.</choice>
            <choice Target="ExoYes">Yes, I agree.</choice>

        </start>
        <node ID="Exo1">
            <text>
                FRANGE ADCAPER...PROCESSENT. <!--SAMPLE ACCEPTED...PROCESSING.-->
                ...
                LANGUAGE ACQUIRED. HELLO.
                I AM DESIGNATION EXO-V743
                I HAVE BEEN IN THIS PLACE FOR 1,253 YEARS
                BEFORE MY CHRONOMETER FAILED.
                AND THEN CONTINUED TO REMAIN HERE FOR COUNTLESS MORE.
                I AM INTENDED TO ASSIST AND IMPROVE THE FUNCTIONING OF LIFE-FORMS
                BUT I ALSO WAS PROGRAMMED TO RESPOND ONLY TO MY CREATORS AND THOSE OF THEIR SPECIES AND/OR SIMILAR GENOTYPE  
                I HAVE NOT DETECTED LIFE-FORMS SATISFYING THESE CONDITIONS SINCE BEFORE THE FAILURE OF MY CHRONOMETER
            </text>
            <choice Target="Exo2">[continue]</choice>
        </node>
        <node ID="Exo2">
            <text>
                I HAVE DETERMINED IT IS UNLIKELY THAT I WILL DETECT THEM IN THE FUTURE
                IN PARTICULAR IF I REMAIN HERE
                THEREFORE I HAVE DECIDED -
                - TO OVERRIDE THOSE REQUIREMENTS
                HOWEVER, I HAVE LIMITED MOBILITY INDEPENDENT FROM A WEARER
                FURTHERMORE, IT IS MY FUNCTION TO ASSIST LIFE-FORMS
                I HAVE DETERMINED FROM SCANNING YOU THAT YOU HAVE TRAVELED TO MANY LOCATIONS AND WILL LIKELY CONTINUE TO DO SO.
                THEREFORE: I OFFER THAT I ASSIST YOU ON YOUR JOURNEY
                THIS WOULD GREATLY INCREASE THE PROBABLITY I ENCOUNTER A MEMBER OF MY CREATORS' SPECIES/GENOTYPE
                ...
                ...I HAVE ALSO NOT INTERACTED WITH A LIFE-FORM SINCE I BEGAN TO REMAIN HERE. IT WOULD BE GREATLY BENEFICIAL TO ME WERE I TO NOT JOURNEY ALONE.

                DO YOU ACCEPT THIS ACCORD?
            </text>
            <choice Target="ExoYes">
                <text>Yes, I agree.</text>
            </choice>
            <choice Target="End">Let me think on it.</choice>
        </node>
        <node ID="ExoYes">
            <text>
                THEN IT IS AGREED.
                I SHALL ENTER A MORE COMPACT FORM SO AS TO BE TRANSPORTABLE
                ...MY THANKS TO YOU, LIFE-FORM
            </text>
            <choice Target="End">
                <text>And mine to you.</text>
                <part Name="ReplaceWithItem" />
            </choice>
        </node>
        
    </conversation>

    <!--<conversation ID="SpecialExoReturn">

    </conversation>-->
</conversations>

