<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<books>
  <book ID="Xenonutrition" Title="{{W|A Primer on Xeno-Nutrition}}" Format="Auto" Margins="1,2,2,2">
 <page>
{{C|By Sixshrew}}

{{y|I.
It was once stated, "A guest never forgets the host who has treated him kindly."

However, in the author's experience, the opposite proves to be true. More often than not, the guest is under the impression that one is entitled to everything that the host has to offer, and would seek to redress any perceived slight by an incessant pestering of the poor host, if they do not escalate to outright violence. In the jungles of Qud, especially, there is often wisdom in discretion, and in appeasing those who would be more trouble otherwise.


II.
Most visitors possess means of movement, hence the focus on ambulatory beings. Regardless, the information contained herein ought to be generalizable to the hosting of most intelligent life forms. For unintelligent life forms, it is suggested that one be as hostile as possible instead.

This set of tablets thus focuses on the provision of nutriment, one of the common causes for robbery or visitations.

III.
Chaos is inevitable. All beings will, eventually, give way to chaos as the underlying order of their being breaks down. In siphoning the inherent order within other structures, the lifeform can forestall its doom. Nutrition will be defined henceforth as the process in which a lifeform uses an object with low local entropy to reduce its local entropy. Nutrition will also be defined as the object with such low entropy, often created by acts of arrangement and chemistry.

Organisms vary in their needs and function, and this influences the nutrition that is appropriate and possible for them. Highly ambulatory beings, generally, require a high amount of energy in order to sustain their frivolous motions, necessitating greater arrangement of nutrition. As a general rule of thumb, they typically prefer the similar class of beings to sustain them, such as a human would generally need to consume other animals, and cragmenschen generally need to consume minerals. 

IV.
As an exhaustive description of all possible nutrition would require a prohibitive amount of tablets, the author will describe the preparation of the most popular nutrition in their current place of residence, the Goat in Sweet Leaf.

The Goat in Sweet Leaf is the prototypical foodstuff for animals. It is prepared from deceased goats, deceased bananas, and seasoned with honey and salt. As the author possesses more efficient means of acquiring nutrition,  it will be left as an exercise for a competent cook to determine the correct proportions of seasoning and ingredients.

V.
First, the goat is produced by feeding two or more goats with almost any organic material, such as banana leaves. A new goat will eventually be created if enough goats are brought together, in a process analogous to pollination, if it was wet and bloody. The author mentions this as it is often wise to replenish one's supply of goats. One must be warned that the goat must be killed in order to obtain their meat, which is used in making the dish. Such endeavors may prove to be highly dangerous.

Secondly, bananas are then retrieved from banana trees. The process of replenishing bananas should not require any special intervention beyond keeping the banana trees healthy and in fertile soil, under tropical climate. The bananas are left to dry under the sun. Care should be taken to prevent contamination of the bananas. The bananas may also become contaminated if left in the sun for longer than a year. Ideally, 3 months of sun-drying is sufficient to produce a dark brown hue that the author presumes is pleasing to highly ambulatory beings. One must be warned that the banana must be maimed in order to obtain their fruit and leaves, which are used in making the dish. Such endeavors may prove to be highly dangerous.

Third, the honey is obtained from a bear, though the author is not privy to the manufacturing process. As far as the author is concerned, it involves "honeycombs", which are bear egg sacs that are left upon trees, before being retrieved by the larvae's parents and the sacs repurposed for consumption. One will be relieved to learn that killing honeycombs is very easy and painless.

The final ingredient, salt, is made into seasoning by grinding them to a coarse powder. Salt is a popular choice as they are fragile and therefore require the least exertion to process, but the author, personally, would elect to use rarer minerals such as agate, to further impress the guests.

VI.
With all ingredients gathered, the raw goat meat is roasted on a pan and manipulated with a heat-resistant tool to cause even burning of the meat. The burning should be performed for a short period of time, ending as soon as the meat turns brown and soft, and before it carbonizes.

As soon as the goat is ready, sliced sun-dried bananas are placed into the pan, and moved around the pan alongside the goat meat to impart the scent of goat on the bananas.

Finally, banana leaves flavored with honey and salt are used as the base upon which the goats and bananas are placed. Curiously, the author have never witnessed a guest fully consuming the leaves.

If the reader has taken care to follow the recipe thus far, one may be able to achieve the reward of cooking as mentioned prior. The author, personally, was capable of impressing those that have tried the dish, such that xe was asked never to cook again.
  </page>
</book>
</books>