<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<books>
	<book ID="Hazzary453_amhf_WellDiary" Title="{{W|Record of Events: The pilgrim in the well}}" Format="Auto" Margins="1,2,2,2">
		<page>
{{c|Begin record.}}

A pilgrim has tripped as they were sacrificing their offerings into the well, falling in head-first. Everyone thought they had died instantly to the plasmatic core, until several minutes later when their shouts for help could be heard.

Everyone is confused, and no one seems to be able to figure out what to do. Eschelstadt, the priest is acting like nothing has happened at all, they're preaching even louder than normal. I think they're trying to drown out the pilgrim's shouts. It isn't working. The other pilgrims are wondering why the core hasn't destroyed them, some are saying the core was never meant to destroy something as large as a person, and others are wondering if Shekhinah themself is protecting them. Others still are saying they have defiled the well.

I'm going to go get the warden.
</page>
<page>
The warden has taken control of the situation. Well, they're trying at least. First, she sent someone to see if any of the merchants had a recoiler for sale. It doesn't look like they had any luck. Now she is trying to negotiate a temporary closure of the well, but Eschelstadt is refusing. Sentiment among the other pilgrims is turning against the man in the well. I hope none of them sacrifice anything dangerous.
</page>
<page>
By Resheph! The pilgrims are throwing steel chairs down the well!
</page>
<page>
The warden has enlisted a tinkerer from the silt grounds to see if they can develop a way to safely get them out. They've also brought some supplies to help the victim, some bandages, and a salve injector to treat their injuries.
</page>
<page>
The man in the well is starting to draw a crowd. Some of the merchants are trying to take advantage of the spectacle. They've set up near the entrance to the Stilt to sell all kinds of things for people to throw down the well most of it is helpful such as food and other provisions. 

One particularly unscrupulous merchant tried to sell bricks. The warden evicted them quickly. Not quickly enough to stop the pilgrims from buying up most of his stock.
</page>
<page>
Eschelstadt is all but refusing to help. They seem to think adding a "Watch your step" sign is enough.
</page>
<page>
The tinkerer's work has been destroyed. No one quite knows who did it, but the warden suspects it was one of the Merchants. I'm inclined to agree, I don't think they want the crowd to leave. This whole debacle has been very profitable for them.
</page>
<page>
The tinkerer has made a crane to get someone safely down the well to rescue the man trapped there, but no one is volunteering. Everyone thinks it's too dangerous. If someone doesn't go soon, they're going to be rescuing a corpse.
</page>
	</book>
</books>